afnpacific.net 2015-03-18

# American Forces Network Pacific > Home

American Forces Network Pacific is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the American Forces Network Pacific Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the American Forces Network Pacific website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

American Forces Network Pacific collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. American Forces Network Pacific also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by American Forces Network Pacific. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by American Forces Network Pacific for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the American Forces Network Pacific Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through American Forces Network Pacific public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: American Forces Network Pacific does not read any of your private online communications.

American Forces Network Pacific encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from American Forces Network Pacific so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. American Forces Network Pacific is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the American Forces Network Pacific and American Forces Network Pacific family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

American Forces Network Pacific collects and uses your personal information to operate the American Forces Network Pacific Web site and deliver the services you have requested. American Forces Network Pacific also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from American Forces Network Pacific and its affiliates. American Forces Network Pacific may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

American Forces Network Pacific does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. American Forces Network Pacific may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, American Forces Network Pacific may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to American Forces Network Pacific, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

American Forces Network Pacific does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

American Forces Network Pacific keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within American Forces Network Pacific, in order to determine what American Forces Network Pacific services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within American Forces Network Pacific to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

American Forces Network Pacific Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on American Forces Network Pacific or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of American Forces Network Pacific; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of American Forces Network Pacific, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The American Forces Network Pacific Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize American Forces Network Pacific pages, or register with American Forces Network Pacific site or services, a cookie helps American Forces Network Pacific to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same American Forces Network Pacific Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the American Forces Network Pacific features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the American Forces Network Pacific services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

American Forces Network Pacific secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. American Forces Network Pacific secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

American Forces Network Pacific will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. American Forces Network Pacific encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how American Forces Network Pacific is protecting your information.

Contact Information

American Forces Network Pacific welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that American Forces Network Pacific has not adhered to this Statement, please contact American Forces Network Pacific at [afnweb@gmail.com](mailto:afnweb@gmail.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
